// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following families is characterised by trimerous flowers, superior and trilocular ovary with axile placentation?",
    answer: " Liliaceae",
    options: [
      " Liliaceae",
      "Solanaceae",
      " Cucurbitaceae",
      "Compositae"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following sentences is incorrect?",
    answer: "The total mass of protons and electrons in the atom",
    options: [
      "Nuclear binding energy is the energy released in the formation of an atom from subatomic particles.",

      "It the nucleus was formed from initially separated protons and electrons then the amount of matter converted into energy was called Mass defect.",

      "The total mass of protons and electrons in the atom.",

      "The most stable nuclei are molecules with the highest binding energy."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is incorrect for Fabaceae?",
    answer: " Actinomorphic flower",
    options: [
      "Actinomorphic flower",
      "Monocarpellary superior ovary",
      " Vexillary aestivation",
      "Legume fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Tetradynamous stamen is a characteristic feature of",
    answer: "Cruciferae",
    options: [
      "Cruciferae",
      "Malvaceae",
      "Liliaceae",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Obligately placed superior ovary is the characteristic of?",
    answer: "Solanaceae",
    options: [
      "Fabaceae",
      "Brassicaceae",
      "Solanaceae",
      " Compositae"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " A nucleus of uranium decays at rest into nuclei of thorium and helium. Then?",
    answer: "The helium nucleus has more kinetic energy than the thorium nucleus",
    options: [
      "The helium nucleus has more kinetic energy than the thorium nucleus",
      "The helium nucleus has less momentum than the thorium nucleus",
      "The helium nucleus has more momentum than the thorium nucleus",
      "The helium nucleus has less kinetic energy than the thorium nucleus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Haversian canals occur in?",
    answer: "Humerus",
    options: [
      "Scapula",
      "Humerus",
      "Clavicle",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Mammalian pinna is supported by?",
    answer: "Elastic cartilage",
    options: [
      "Elastic cartilage",
      "Calcified cartilage",
      "Hyaline cartilage",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Major inorganic components of vertebrate bone is",
    answer: "calcium phosphate",
    options: [
      "Potassium hydroxide",
      "Calcium phosphate",
      "Calcium carbonate",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " A person travels 10 km North and 20 km East. What will be the displacement from the initial point?",
    answer: "22.36 km",
    options: [
      "20 km",
      "22.36 km",
      "30 km",
      "32.36 km"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];